COLE WILLIAMS

Full Stack Developer



PROFILE

I am Fullstack
Web Developer based in
Denver, with an interest in
solving new problems
everyday, both in code and
in life!

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML5 - 3 Years CSS3 - 3 Years Javascript - 2 Years AngularJS - 2 Years MongoDB - 2 Years

Bootstrap - Gulp SQL - MySQL Wordpress - Web Design Git UI/UX development

CONTACT



(720) 883-6040



Wcole2222@gmail.com



www.colewill.com

OTHER INTERESTS

In my free time you can find me playing Catan, Rock Climbing, Hiking, floating down rivers, walking my dogs, or discovering new breweries around Denver.

WEB DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE

JOYLAB - WEB DEVELOPER - FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

Currently working as a Jr. Web Developer for a Denver Based digital Agency. My day to day tasks include deploying websites using Git/Bash/Linux. Writing HTML5 + CSS3, and generating reports with Ruby + SQL queries. WebDesign and optimization with Wordpress. And custom development needs with Javascript.

LATITUDE40 - FULL STACK DEVELOPER - AUGUST 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

Worked as a contractor on several MEAN stack apps for a Denver Based Software Consulting Firm. MongoDB, AngularJS, NodeJS, Javascript, HTML5, and CSS3.

SKINNY GLOW LIPO - WEB DEVELOPER - JUNE 2017 - PRESENT

HTML5 - CSS3 - Bootstrap - Javascript - Sketch Freelance Web Developer for a Denver Based Small Business

INTEGRATIONS DEVELOPER -- MJ FREEWAY - SEP 2017 - JAN 2018

Was a part of the Dev team for the State of Washington's Cannabis traceability API. I worked with Node.js, cURL, HTML, CSS, and handled QA testing of the API and helped 3rd party developers with software support.

EDUCATION

METROPOLITAN STATE UNIVERSITY OF DENVER

2014-2015 -- Pre-Medical Studies

Biology I+II, Physics I+II, Anatomy/Physiology I+II, Chemistry I+II -- 3.6 GPA

COLORADO UNIVERSITY OF BOULDER

2005 - 2010

Bachelor of Arts, Major in Saxophone - Jazz + Classical

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INSIDE SALES REPRESENTATIVE -- DISH NETWORK

May 2016 - Mar 2017

I handled 15-20 inbound sales calls per day, and had 30min to 1hr conversations with prospective customers. I sold Home Television and Internet subscriptions, scheduled installations, and was responsible for building trust and positive brand awareness.

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP - GENERAL ASSEMBLY - DENVER

WeWork Lohi Denver | March 2017 - June 2017

Full-Time Immersive Web Development Bootcamp: 600hrs of Front + Back End Web Development Training, Study and Practice. AngularJS, Javascript, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, MongoDB